Miklos Rozsa Papers
Miklos Rozsa Papers
- Non-commercial recordings
  - Audiotapes
    - Glendale Symphony Orchestra [Intermission and second half], 12/18/1960; rozsa_055; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Glendale Symphony Orchestra [second half of broadcast], 12/18/1960; rozsa_135; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Hamilton Philharmonic, 9/23-24, 1977; rozsa_023; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 120 (Oversize 356)
      Concert Overture (1&2); Hungarian Serenage (2); Theme Variations and Finale (1&2); El Cid: Prelude (2), Love Theme (2&1), March (2); Spellbound: "Concerto" (2); Ben-Hur: Prelude (1), Mother’s Love (1), Love Theme (2), Burning Desert (2), The Rowing of the Galley Slaves (2), Parade (2&1); Thief of Bagdad: Princess (2) [Numbers in parentheses indicate concert number one or two]
    - Hawaii Concert, Overture to Symphony Concert Nocturne Ungherese, rozsa_007; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Hawaii Concert and Spellbound Concerto, rozsa_080; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Hawaii Concert, Piano Concert, rozsa_082; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Hawaii Concert: Intermission Discussion Theme, Variations, and Finale, rozsa_012; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Hungarian Program: Hungarians in the World, rozsa_037; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 19:30 (Oversize 356)
    - Ivanhoe and Plymouth Adventure, rozsa_137; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - John Green, 6/3/1974; rozsa_078; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Jungle Book, rozsa_030; Leo Glenn, Narrator, The Frankenland State Symphony Orchestra; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Jungle Book, rozsa_128; Leo Genn, Narrator; Miklos Rozsa, Conductor; The Frankenland State Symphony Orchestra; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Jungle Book, rozsa_199; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - The Jungle Book, Feb 1956; Cameron Mitchell, Narrator and Harold Scott, Conductor; rozsa_156; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - The Jungle Book with BBC Welsh Orchestra, 12/21/1973; rozsa_040; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30 (Oversize 357)
    - Kaleidoscope [with U.S.M.A. Band], rozsa_175; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - KFAC Interview with Steve [Markham], 3/2/1975; rozsa_041; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - KFAC Interview with Steve Markham, 3/2/1975; rozsa_161; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Knights of the Round Table; Diane; Story of 3 Loves; Young Bess, 3/2/1975; rozsa_068; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - [Korda; Thief of Baghdad], rozsa_070; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Last Embrace [missing], 12/13-14, 1978; rozsa_122; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - [illegible] Life Story, rozsa_035; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [illegible] Life Story, rozsa_088; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - London (2) (Feyder), rozsa_064; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - London Filmharmonic, rozsa_123; El Cid March; El Cid Love Theme; Life of Sherlock Holmes; King of Kings; Lydia Waltz; Spellbound; Ben-Hur Prelude; Ben-Hur Love Theme; Ben-Hur March; Quo Vadis March; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Lost Weekend with Synthesizer, 3 tracks; rozsa_033; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Lust for Life, rozsa_150; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Lybia [missing], rozsa_146; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Medieval Spanish Music, rozsa_103; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Mikloes Rozsa: Konzert fur Violine und Orchester Op. 24, 6/22/1966; rozsa_196; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Miklos Rozsa Duo for Violin and Piano Performed by Manuel and Sara Compinsky, rozsa_091; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Miklos Rozsa on his Filmscoring: An Interview and Music Special as Aired on WETA-FM, 1976; rozsa_126; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Mozart a Major Sonata, Tema con variations Op. 29/a, rozsa_081; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Music in England [and] English and Conducting, rozsa_072; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Music From the Films, 3/10/1957; rozsa_117; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Musique du Viet-Nam [and] Chants Populaire du Viet-Nam, rozsa_095; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Notturno Ungherese, Op. 28, 11/4/1963; rozsa_052; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Notturno Ungherese, Op. 28, 11/24/1962; rozsa_152; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Notturno Ungherese, Op. 28, 4/18/1964; rozsa_153; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Passionmusik for Choir, Soloist, & Orchestra, 2/28/1978; rozsa_042; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Pearl Caveman [missing], rozsa_139; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Pema Music "Providence", rozsa_192; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Piano Concert with Leonard Pennario and the Philadelphia Orchestra, rozsa_038; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Piano Concerto, rozsa_111; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Piano Concerto Leonard Pennario [illegible], rozsa_075; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Piano Concerto, Toccata Capricciosa, Quo Vadis, Young Bess, Greatest Story Ever Told, 1/9/1977; 4/2/1977; rozsa_022; Piano Concerto (Pennario, Schermerhorn, Milwaukee Symphony), Toccata Capricciosa (Hoffman, cello), Quo Vadis (Excerpts), Young Bess (Suite, Simon Brimmer, organist), Greatest Story Ever Told (Newman, Finale to Act I); 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Piano Concerto: Pennario and Philadelphia Orchestra, rozsa_083; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Piano Sonata, rozsa_121; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Piano Sonata, rozsa_061; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
      Movement I: Calmo; Movement II: Andante con Calore; Movement III: Allegro Giusto e Vigoroso
    - Program of Avant Garde Music, rozsa_019; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Providence], rozsa_074; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - [Providence], rozsa_076; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Quintette in F-Minor for Piano and Strings, 11/23/1974; rozsa_043; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Quo Vadis (from MGM 78 RPM Records), rozsa_016; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Quo Vadis (from MGM Records), rozsa_031; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Rhapsody of Steel, rozsa_039; First half orchestra only, second half narrated by Gary Merrill; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 45 (Oversize 357)
    - Rome Interview, rozsa_166; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Rozsa: Fedora (1 of 3), rozsa_204; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Rozsa: Fedora (2 of 3), rozsa_203; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Rozsa: Fedora (3 of 3), rozsa_202; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Rozsa: Leaving England, U.S.A., rozsa_014; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Rozsa Original Violin Rousert with Denes Zsigmondy], rozsa_159; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - [San Francisco], rozsa_085; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - San Francisco State Concert, 1/24/1965; rozsa_087; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Schumann IV Symphony, 4th movement, Band 2 [illegible] und absage [illegible] [missing], rozsa_084; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Second String Quartet, Op. 22 [Played by the Compinsky String Quartet], rozsa_168; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, 'Cello, and Orchestra, Op. 29, 9/22/1966; rozsa_101; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, 'Cello, and Orchestra, Op. 29, 1/6/1978; rozsa_113; Victor Aitay, violin; Frank Miller, 'cello; Chicago Symphony Orchestra; Erich Leinsdorf, conductor.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, Op. 29, rozsa_001; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, Op. 29, rozsa_125; With Alice & Eleanor Schoenfeld as soloists and Jean Koetsier as Conductor; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Cello, & Orchestra, Op. 29, rozsa_062; Südfunk, Sinfonieorchester; Violin, Alice Schoenfeld; Cello, Eleanore Schoenfeld; Conductor, Jiri Starék; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:35 (Oversize 357)
    - Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Violoncello and Orchestra, rozsa_127; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:15 (Oversize 359)
    - Sinfonia Concertante Op. 296, rozsa_018; Josef Suk, Violonist; Janos Starker, Cellist; Gyorgy Lehel, Conductor; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Sodom and Gomorah, rozsa_191; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah [reel I], rozsa_020; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah [reel II], rozsa_047; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Someko Singers Concert; Retakes of "Sailing Homeward" and "The Cuckoo", 4/13/1986; rozsa_057; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Sonatina for Clarinet Solo, Op. 27, Earl Thomas, Clarinetist recorded at Interlochen, 6/30/1971; rozsa_004; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Spellbound (from Warner Brothers/Heindorf Album), rozsa_008; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - String Trio Op. 1/a and Interview with Martin Bookspan, Edward Downs, and Robert Jacobson, New York Critics, 12/30/1975; rozsa_003; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [illegible] Symphony Broadcast, rozsa_073; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Tartalom, Zongoraverseny/magyarorszagi bemutato felvetele/eloadja: Tusa Erzsebet es az allami Hangversenyzenekar, vezenyel Ferencsik janos, 1968; rozsa_011; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Tema con Variazioni, Op. 29a, Rózsa; Talin, Concerto for Viola & String Orchestra, Hovhaness, 1952; 1962; rozsa_048; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - The Thief of Baghdad; A Double Life; Lost Weekend; A Time to Love and a Time to Die; The Naked City, 3/2/1975; rozsa_067; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Theme, Variations and Finale, rozsa_201; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Theme, Variations and Finale, Op. 13, rozsa_200; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Thief of Baghdad and Vansittart, rozsa_094; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Time After Time, 3/30/1979; rozsa_114; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Time After Time, 3/30/1979; rozsa_115; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - A Time to Love and a Time to Die, rozsa_053; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - A Time to Love and a Time to Die, rozsa_105; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - To Everything There is a Season, 6/3/1961; rozsa_063; The Mitzefelt Chorale at the International Music Festival; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - To Everything There is a Season, 10/16/1951; rozsa_198; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - To Everything There is a Season, rozsa_162; Pacific Lutheran University Choir; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - To Everything There is a Season with the Mitzelfelt Chorale at the International Music Festival, 6/3/1961; rozsa_129; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Tripartita, 10/14/1976; rozsa_054; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Tripartita, rozsa_066; Felsenkirche Broadcast; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Tripartita, 10/12-13, 1976; rozsa_102; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Tripartita, Op. 33, rozsa_060; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Tripartita per Orchestra Op. 33, rozsa_021; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Two Motets: The Vanities of Life and the Seasons, rozsa_155; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Two Songs; Kaleidoscope; a Madrigal of Spring; Festive Flourish, rozsa_131; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Two Songs, Op. 16, Six Bagatelles, Op. 12, rozsa_029; Op. 16 with Ethel Armeling, Contralto and Frank Dewald, Piano; Op. 12 number one with Frank Dewald, orchestrator (a student performance), numbers four through 6 with David Gideon, Piano; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - The Vanities of Life, rozsa_163; Pacific Lutheran University Choir; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Vaughan Williams: Flos Campi; Newman:The Greatest Story Ever Told; Tarantella; Herrmann: Berceuse: For the Fallen; Rozsa: A Double Life; Madame Bovary; Bagatelles, rozsa_104; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
      Vaughan Williams: Flos Campi; Newman:The Greatest Story Ever Told; Tarantella; Herrmann: Berceuse: For the Fallen; Rozsa: A Double Life; Madame Bovary; Bagatelles
    - The Vintner’s Daughter, 4/23/1954; rozsa_158; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - The Vinter’s Daughter (Variations on a French Folksong), rozsa_036; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Vintner's Daughter [missing], 9/26/1955; rozsa_149; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Vinter’s Daughter Outtakes Var. 9 to end, rozsa_195; Outtakes Var. 9 to end and [illegible] no. 2; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - The Vintner’s Daughter; Hungarian Serenade; the Vienna Symphony Orchestra, rozsa_069; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - The Vintner’s Daughter with Frankenland State Symphony, rozsa_120; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - The Vintner’s Daughter: Twelve Variations on a French Folksong, Op. 23a; North-Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances for Violin and Orchestra with Oliver Colbenston on Violin; Hungarian Serenade for Small Orchestra, rozsa_056; The Frankenland Symphony conducted by Erich Kloss; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Viola Concerto [missing], rozsa_090; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Violin Concerto, rozsa_089; Possibly Op. 24; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Violin Concerto (Hamburg -- Goldenberg), rozsa_010; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - The Voice of Johannes Brahms, rozsa_099; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Works of Jack Gallagher, rozsa_034; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - WQXR, Live Broadcast of Miklos Rozsa Birthday Program, 4/18/1977; rozsa_028; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [unknown], rozsa_015; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #1], rozsa_002; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #2], rozsa_005; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #3], rozsa_025; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #4], rozsa_032; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #5], rozsa_071; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #6], rozsa_077; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #7], rozsa_079; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #8], rozsa_097; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #9], rozsa_108; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #10], rozsa_110; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #11], rozsa_118; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - [Untitled Rozsa Tape #12], rozsa_119; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
  - Phonograph records
    This series contains phonodiscs in various sizes and formats. Phonodiscs are not boxed, and should be requested by title and ID number. For example, for the first item below, ask for "L’Arbre Blanc, item rozsa_252."
    - L’Arbre Blanc, rozsa_252; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Because of Him, rozsa_207; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben-Hur, 5/31/1973; rozsa_243; Recorded by P. Bush; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben Hur (Part 1), 5/31/1973; rozsa_247; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben-Hur (Part 3), rozsa_249; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben Hur (Parts 3-4), 5/31/1973; rozsa_244; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben Hur (Parts 5-6), 5/31/1973; rozsa_245; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben Hur (Parts 7-8), 5/31/1973; rozsa_246; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Ben Hur: Love Theme, 6/10/1959; rozsa_248; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Brute Force, rozsa_235; The Doctor Leaves; Preparation; The Break; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Crisis, 4/15/1950; rozsa_217; Main Title; End Title; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Crisis, 2/1/1950; rozsa_218; Vincinte Gomez; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Double Indemnity (Parts 1 and 2), rozsa_250; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Double Indemnity (Parts 3-4), rozsa_251; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Double Indemnity (Parts 7-8), rozsa_262; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Duo for Violoncello and Piano, Op. 8, rozsa_293; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Emma’s Waltz, rozsa_214; long version; short version; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Emma’s Waltz, rozsa_231; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Four Feathers, rozsa_209; Recorded by Will Day; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Franck: Symphony in D-Minor; Movements II and III, rozsa_237; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Gloria, rozsa_211; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Gloria, rozsa_213; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Gloria], rozsa_212; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Interview with Miklos Rozsa, rozsa_221; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Interview with Miklos Rozsa, 3/2/1952; rozsa_282; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Jungle Book and Blind Flight, rozsa_229; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Liszt: Mephisto Waltz; De Falla: The Three-Cornered Hat Dances, rozsa_236; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Los Angeles County Museum Program, 3/9/1947; rozsa_275; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Los Angeles County Symphony, 4/20/1946; rozsa_268; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Macomber Affair, rozsa_279; Main Titles; Safari; Love Reborn; Man and Beast; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Macomber Affair and The NBC Symphony Orchestra Presents "The Miraculous Mandarin", 12/15/1946; rozsa_290; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Madame Bovary’s Waltz, 6/27/1957; rozsa_177; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Miklos Rozsa and the Standard Symphony of San Francisco Part 1, 7/6/1947; rozsa_284; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Miklos Rozsa and the Standard Symphony of San Francisco Part 2, 7/6/1947; rozsa_283; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Miklos Rozsa and the Standard Symphony of San Francisco Part 5 and The Score of "A Double Life", 7/6/1947; 6/13/1948; rozsa_289; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Music from "The Lost Week-end" Prudential Family Hour, 1/13/1946; rozsa_260; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Naked City, Despair and Epilogue, rozsa_223; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Naked City, Notturno, rozsa_225; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Naked City, Prologue to Murder and Scherzo, rozsa_224; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Naked City, Pursuit, Mar 10 [no year]; rozsa_222; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Naked City, Pursuit and Epilogue, rozsa_227; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [The Naked City] Part #3: Scherzo and Part #4: Despair, rozsa_238; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [The Naked City] Part #5: Pursuit and Part #6: Epilogue, 4/27/1948; rozsa_239; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [The Naked City] Scherzo and Despair, rozsa_226; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra, 11/14/1943; rozsa_271; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra, 11/14/1943; rozsa_273; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Notturno Ungherese, Op. 28, rozsa_183; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Pastorkle Danza, 3/19/1943; rozsa_277; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Philharmonic, rozsa_234; VinylDisc
    - Piano Concerto Part 1 of 2, rozsa_265; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Piano Concerto Part 2 of 2, rozsa_266; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Piano Sonata, rozsa_267; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Piano Sonata, rozsa_274; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Piano Sonata and the Naked City, 2/2/1949; rozsa_296; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Prologue to Murder; Notturno part 2, rozsa_219; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Prologue to Murder; Notturno part 2, rozsa_220; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rozsa and Bowl [Double Life Fantasy] Part 1, rozsa_276; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rozsa and Bowl [Double Life Fantasy] Part 2-4, rozsa_295; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rozsa and Bowl [Double Life Fantasy] Part 5-7, rozsa_294; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rozsa and Bowl [Double Life Fantasy] Part 6-8, rozsa_291; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rozsa and Bowl [Double Life Fantasy] Part 10-12, rozsa_292; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rubinstein Philharmonic Concert, rozsa_285; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rubinstein Philharmonic Concert, rozsa_286; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rubinstein Philharmonic Concert, rozsa_287; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Rubinstein Philharmonic Concert [end of 3rd movement and last movement], rozsa_288; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Sonata for Two Violins, 5/5/1948; rozsa_278; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Strange Love and I Suppose It’s Love, Part one of "The Red House", 3/14/1947; rozsa_270; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Serenade (Part 1), 6/8/1946; rozsa_242; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Serenade (Parts 2 and 3), 6/8/1946; rozsa_241; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Since Time Began, rozsa_261; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Sonata for Piano 2nd and 3rd Movements, rozsa_272; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Spellbound, rozsa_206; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Spellbound, 8/17/1946; rozsa_215; Hollywood Bowl; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Spring Pastoral for Large Orchestra, rozsa_240; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Test Pressing of Blood on the Sun, rozsa_232; CT 6031 (Notes on sleeve by Miklos Rozsa); VinylDisc
    - Test Pressing of Knights of the Round Table, 3/24/1980; rozsa_233; STV-81128; VinylDisc
    - Theme Variations and Finale, 4/3/1948; rozsa_263; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - To Everything There’s a Season, rozsa_264; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Two Dances from the Motion Picture 'Madame Bovary’, 12/25/1949; rozsa_230; The Standard Oil Company of California Presents "Two Dances from the Motion Picture 'Madame Bovary’"; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Thief of Baghdad, rozsa_210; A.K.Z. Dunn Song; T4 Piano and Voice; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Thief of Baghdad: O Throbbing Heart, rozsa_208; Adelaide Hall; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Thief of Baghdad: Sabu’s Sailor Song, rozsa_258; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Thief of Baghdad: Seaman’s Song, rozsa_259; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - VIP Love Theme, rozsa_182; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Winston Churchill Part 1, 3/31/1949; rozsa_281; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Winston Churchill Part 4, 3/31/1949; rozsa_280; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Works Progress Administration Program 27, 1942; rozsa_305; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Works Progress Administration Program 27, 1942; rozsa_306; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #1], rozsa_205; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #2], 2/10/1947; rozsa_216; Production 10007; takes 10BB2; no. 836; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #3], rozsa_253; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #4], rozsa_254; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #5], rozsa_255; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #6], rozsa_256; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #7], rozsa_257; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #8], rozsa_269; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #9], rozsa_297; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #10], rozsa_298; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #11], 2/15/1945; rozsa_299; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #12], 2/15/1945; rozsa_300; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #13], 2/15/1945; rozsa_301; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #14], 2/15/1945; rozsa_302; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #15], 2/15/1945; rozsa_303; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - [Untitled Rozsa Disc #16], rozsa_304; Lacquer discs/acetates
- Writings
  - By Rózsa
    - Evans, Mark - Soundtrack: The Music of the Movies (Introduction by Rózsa) (Box 71)
    - Johnson, Edward, Bernard Herrmann: Hollywood's Music-Dramatist (Foreword by Rózsa) (Box 71)
    - Lists, Drafts, and Notes (Box 71)
    - Music Fragments (Box 71)
    - Rózsa Miklós: Életem történeteiből (Box 71)
    - Writings, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - By others
    - Ambrus, Edith, The Proof, screenplay (Box 72)
    - Kiss, Martin Kerecsendi, Beyond the Seven Seas (Box 72)